<DialogueDatabase>
  <Dialogue>
    <ID>0</ID>
    <Lines>
	  <Line>Great job at completing the stage!</Line>
      <Line>We have just unlocked a new spell from the previous stage. Let's check it out!</Line>
	  <Line>Go to the &lt;b&gt;Spells&lt;/b&gt; tab and I'll explain more there.</Line>
    </Lines>
   </Dialogue>
   <Dialogue>
	<ID>1</ID>
	<Lines>
		<Line>In this tab, you can see the spells that you currently have unlocked.</Line>
		<Line>You can view and change your equipped spells in this tab before heading out to your next expedition.</Line>
		<Line>Simply drag the spell you would like to equip from your spell inventory to your equipped spells.</Line>
		<Line>We have unlocked an electroshock spell from the previous stage.</Line>
		<Line>Go and equip the electroshock spell to your equipped spells.</Line>
		<Line>Press the back button once you are done.</Line>
	</Lines>
   </Dialogue>
	<Dialogue>
	<ID>2</ID>
	<Lines>
		<Line>Let’s now take a look at the places we can explore!</Line>
		<Line>Prior to entering a stage, we can take a look at the obstacles that we will encounter.</Line>
		<Line>This allows us to plan our approach before heading out!</Line>
		<Line>Remember to practice &lt;b&gt;problem decomposition.&lt;/b&gt;</Line>
		<Line>Break down the stage into smaller problems and identify which spells to bring in order to accomplish the stage.</Line>
		<Line>Your performance in a stage is denoted by stars.</Line>
		<Line>The number of stars that you receive depends on the number of moves that you perform in the stage.</Line>
		<Line>To earn the maximum number of stars, use your spells effectively throughout the stage!</Line>
		<Line>You can also choose to revisit previous stages to earn more stars.</Line>
		<Line>Lastly, you can view how many stars you have earned on the stages you have played.</Line>
		<Line>Take note that unlocking stages also require attaining a certain amount of stars on the previous stage.</Line>
		<Line>The number of stars needed to unlock the next stage will be displayed here as well.</Line>
		<Line>Enough talk for now. I’m raring to go on our next expedition! Whenever you're ready, let’s head on to the next stage!</Line>
	</Lines>
   </Dialogue>
</DialogueDatabase>