<SpellCode>
<AfterSecondStage>
<ID>0</ID>
<Text>Looks like you have familiarized yourself with using spells to navigate and perform actions of the stage!
</Text>
</AfterSecondStage>

<AfterSecondStage>
<ID>1</ID>
<Bold>Spellcodes</Bold>
<Text>I think it's time you learned about using spellcodes! Head over to the Spellcodes tab
</Text>
<Arrow>Left1</Arrow>
</AfterSecondStage>

<AfterSecondStage>
<ID>2</ID>
<Bold>Spellcodes</Bold>
<Text>Spellcodes are a predefined sequence of spells that you can immediately use to perform certain actions much more efficiently on your action queue!
</Text>
</AfterSecondStage>

<AfterSecondStage>
<ID>3</ID>
<Text>You can add spellcodes to your inventory by pressing the create button.
</Text>
<Arrow>Up1</Arrow>
</AfterSecondStage>

<AfterSecondStage>
<ID>4</ID>
<Text>
Let’s try to make a basic spellcode that will allow us to shoot a fireball and move forward in succession.
</Text>
</AfterSecondStage>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
<ID>5</ID>
  <Text>
    You can create and edit your spellcode in this tab.
  </Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>6</ID>
    <Text>
      You can edit the contents of the spellcode and the spellcode’s name.
    </Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>
  
<AddSpellcodeTab>
  <ID>7</ID>
  <Text>
    To start off, you give the spellcode any name that you like.
  </Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>8</ID>
    <Text>
    Then drag the fireball spell and the move right spell into the spellcode.
    </Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>9</ID>
    <Text>
    Take note that the order the spells are executed in the spellcode are from left to right.
    </Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>10</ID>
    <Text>
      Once you’re done creating the spellcode, click on the Save button.
    </Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>
  
<AddSpellcodeTab>
  <ID>11</ID>
  <Text>PAUSEFORSPELLCODENAME</Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>12</ID>
    <Bold>abstraction</Bold>
    <Text>Always remember to apply the concept of abstraction when performing spells on the stage.</Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>13</ID>
    <Text>Focus on using the spells that you think are relevant in completing the stage!</Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>14</ID>
    <Text>You can also use this concept when creating your spellcodes!</Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>15</ID>
    <Text>Your created spellcodes will be displayed in your inventory below.</Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>16</ID>
    <Text>You can choose to edit them again if you feel like doing so by pressing the edit button. </Text>
    <Arrow>Up3</Arrow>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>17</ID>
    <Text>Or you could rather delete the spellcode instead by pressing the delete button.  </Text>
    <Arrow>Up4</Arrow>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>18</ID>
    <Text>Let’s add the created spellcode to our equipped spellcodes by pressing the equip button. </Text>
    <Arrow>Up2</Arrow>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>19</ID>
    <Text>You can also unequip your spellcodes and return them to your inventory by pressing the unequip button.</Text>
    <Arrow>Up8</Arrow>
</AddSpellcodeTab>

<AddSpellcodeTab>
    <ID>20</ID>
    <Text>Looks like we’re ready to put our spellcode to use! Let’s head to the next stage.</Text>
</AddSpellcodeTab>
  


</SpellCode>