<Tutorial>
	<Enteringthetutorialstage>
		<ID>0</ID>
		<Text>Nice to meet you Player! I am Fairie! Are you ready to go on an adventure?</Text>
	</Enteringthetutorialstage>

	<Enteringthetutorialstage>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>Don’t worry I will be here to assist you whenever we come across something worth noting!</Text>
	</Enteringthetutorialstage>

	<Enteringthetutorialstage>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<Bold>spells</Bold>
		<Text>Let’s start with the basics. You can use spells to perform actions on the stage! </Text>
	</Enteringthetutorialstage>

	<Enteringthetutorialstage>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<Bold>action stack</Bold>
		<Text>This is the action stack. </Text>
    <Arrow>Right1</Arrow>
	</Enteringthetutorialstage>

	<Enteringthetutorialstage>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<Text>Random spells you currently own will spawn periodically in here. </Text>
    <Arrow>Right1</Arrow>
	</Enteringthetutorialstage>

	<Enteringthetutorialstage>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<Bold>action queue</Bold>
		<Text>This is the action queue. </Text>
    <Arrow>Left1</Arrow>
	</Enteringthetutorialstage>

	<Enteringthetutorialstage>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<Text>You can drag your spells from the action stack down here and execute them by pressing run. </Text>
    <Arrow>Left1</Arrow>
	</Enteringthetutorialstage>

	<Enteringthetutorial>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<Text>Let’s try to use movement spells first.</Text>
	</Enteringthetutorial>
  
  <Enteringthetutorial>
		<ID>8</ID>
    <Page>1</Page>
		<Text>Drag the move left and move right spells from the action stack down to your action queue.</Text>
	</Enteringthetutorial>

	<Enteringthetutorial>
		<ID>9</ID>
    <Page>1</Page>
		<Text>Try to go to the exclamation point in front of you using your movement spells. </Text>
	</Enteringthetutorial>

	<Onceneartheiceblock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<Text>Note that you can perform up to three spells at a time!</Text>
	</Onceneartheiceblock>

	<Onceneartheiceblock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<Text>The sequence in which your spells take effect is from left to right in your action queue!</Text>
	</Onceneartheiceblock>

	<Onceneartheiceblock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<Text>Plan your spells accordingly and make sure they are on the correct sequence before you execute them.</Text>
	</Onceneartheiceblock>

	<Onceneartheiceblock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<Text>Now… looks like this ice block is obstructing us from getting out of here.</Text>
	</Onceneartheiceblock>

	<Onceneartheiceblock>
		<ID>14</ID>
    <Page>2</Page>
		<Text>If I remember correctly, I think fire can get rid of ice. </Text>
	</Onceneartheiceblock>

	<Destroyingtheiceblock>
		<ID>15</ID>
		<Text>Great job! You managed to melt down the ice cube with a fireball attack. </Text>
	</Destroyingtheiceblock>

	<Destroyingtheiceblock>
		<ID>16</ID>
		<Text>Remember, different elemental attacks affect different obstacles in different ways!</Text>
	</Destroyingtheiceblock>

	<Destroyingtheiceblock>
		<ID>17</ID>
		<Bold>evaluate</Bold>
		<Text>Try to evaluate the stage before you plan your strategy! </Text>
	</Destroyingtheiceblock>

	<Destroyingtheiceblock>
		<ID>18</ID>
		<Bold>recognize a pattern</Bold>
		<Text>Maybe you could recognize a pattern in how elemental attacks affect certain obstacles. </Text>
	</Destroyingtheiceblock>

	<pickingupamaterial>
		<ID>19</ID>
		<Text>Wow look at that! You obtained a piece of metal!</Text>
	</pickingupamaterial>

	<pickingupamaterial>
		<ID>20</ID>
		<Text>Maybe this is something we could use later!</Text>
	</pickingupamaterial>

	

</Tutorial>